Guide to the Yale University Art, Architecture, and Art History Theses and Projects
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Class of 2011 and 2012 portfolios [computer files], 2007-2012; Accession 2012-A-099
  - Andrachuk, James, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
    - 2012 M.Arch I Andrachuk, 2012-A-099.0001; 1 (Box 1)
    - Andrachuk, James, 2012-A-099.0002; 1 (Box 1)
  - Aubin, Christopher Patrick, 2011; 2012-A-099.0003; 1 (Box 1)
  - Bachman, John Taylor, 2012; 2012-A-099.0004; 1 (Box 1)
  - Baer, Bradley Edward, 2011; 2012-A-099.0005; 1 (Box 1)
  - Bauld, Melissa, 2011; 2012-A-099.0006; 1 (Box 1)
  - Bench, David, 2012; 2012-A-099.0007; 1 (Box 1)
  - Bingnear, Hilary Jane, 2011; 2012-A-099.0008; 1 (Box 1)
  - Bloomfield, Emma Jane, 2011; 2012-A-099.0009; 1 (Box 1)
  - Blusewicz, Kevin, 2011; 2012-A-099.0010; 1 (Box 1)
  - Bolos, Christos, 2012; 2012-A-099.0011; 1 (Box 1)
  - Bondaryk, Elizabeth, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
  - Bourke, Jeffrey Andrew, 2012; 2012-A-099.0014; 1 (Box 1)
  - Brooks, Miroslava, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
    - 2011_Spring_M.Arch I_Design_Review Miroslava Brooks, 2012-A-099.0015; 1 (Box 1)
    - Miroslava Brooks 2012_Spring_M.Arch I_Design_Final_Review, 2012-A-099.0016; 1 (Box 1)
  - Brdarski, Marija, 2011; 2012-A-099.0017; 1 (Box 1)
  - Bui, Can Vu, 2012; 2012-A-099.0018; 1 (Box 1)
  - Butterfield, Brian Oliver, 2011; 2012-A-099.0019; 1 (Box 1)
  - Calabro, Vincent, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
    - Vincent Calabro M.Arch I Portfolio 2012, 2012-A-099.0020; 1 (Box 1)
    - Yale School of Architecture 2011-Spring-M.Arch I Design Review Vincent Calabro, 2012-A-099.0021; 1 (Box 1)
  - Carlisle, Stephanie Caius, 2011; 2012-A-099.0022; 1 (Box 1)
  - Cena, Lis, 2011; 2012-A-099.0023; 1 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Amy Elizabeth, 2011; 2012-A-099.0024; 1 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Hao (Nicky), 2012; 2012-A-099.0025; 1 (Box 1)
  - Chapman, Christy Lauren, 2012; 2012-A-099.0026; 1 (Box 1)
  - Chowaniec, Craig Robert, 2012; 2012-A-099.0027; 1 (Box 1)
  - Cigolle, Reid, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
    - Reid Cigolle M.Arch II 2012, 2012-A-099.0028; 1 (Box 1)
    - Spring 2011 Design Review M.Arch II Reid Cigolle, 2012-A-099.0029; 1 (Box 1)
  - Coleman, Nicholas, 2012; 2012-A-099.0030; 1 (Box 1)
  - Connock, Christopher Stuart, 2011; 2012-A-099.0031; 1 (Box 1)
  - Dang, Yijie, 2011; 2012-A-099.0032; 1 (Box 1)
  - DeDonato, Amy, 2012 (Box 1)
    - Amy DeDonato M.Arch I 2012 Portfolio, 2012-A-099.0033; 1 (Box 1)
    - Amy DeDonato M.Arch I 2012 DeDonato-M.Arch I 2012, 2012-A-099.0034; 1 (Box 1)
  - DeSouza, Leticia Wouk Almino, 2011; 2012-A-099.0035; 1 (Box 1)
  - Delahoy, Patrick, 2011; 2012-A-099.0036; 1 (Box 1)
  - Di Tolla, Gina Maria, 2012 (Box 1)
    - Gina Di Tolla, 2012-A-099.0037; 1 (Box 1)
    - Gina Di Tolla, 2012-A-099.0038; 1 (Box 1)
  - Dickens, Daniel Gordon, 2012; 2012-A-099.0039; 1 (Box 1)
  - Dugopolski, Jacob Lawrence, 2011; 2012-A-099.0040; 1 (Box 1)
  - Duryea, Danielle Jessica, 2012 (Box 1)
    - Danielle Duryea M.Arch I 2012 Portfolio, 2012-A-099.0041; 1 (Box 1)
    - Danielle Duryea Portfolio Submission M.Arch I 2012, 2012-A-099.0042; 1 (Box 1)
  - Dwyer, Erin Colleen, 2011; 2012-A-099.0043; 1 (Box 1)
  - Edelman, Frances Sarah, 2011; 2012-A-099.0044; 1 (Box 1)
  - Edick, Kipp Colby, 2010-2011 (Box 1)
    - 2011_Spring_M.Arch I_Graduating_Review_Edick_Kipp, 2012-A-099.0045; 1 (Box 1)
    - 2010_Spring_M.Arch I_Design_Review_Edick_Kipp, 2012-A-099.0046; 1 (Box 1)
  - Estes, Cotton Barrett, 2012; 2012-A-099.0047; 1 (Box 1)
  - Everett, Kathryn Joan, 2011; 2012-A-099.0048; 1 (Box 1)
  - Falis, Ilsa Eve, 2012; 2012-A-099.0049; 1 (Box 1)
  - Forman, Avram Michael Kraus, 2012 (Box 1)
    - 2012 Spring M.Arch I Graduating Review Forman Avram, 2012-A-099.0050; 1 (Box 1)
    - Avram Forman M.Arch I 2012 Design Review Portfolio, 2012-A-099.0051; 1 (Box 1)
  - Fox, Will Howard, 2012; 2012-A-099.0052; 1 (Box 1)
  - Fryer, Thomas Matthew Rolles, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
    - Tom Fryer Portfolio 2012, 2012-A-099.0053; 1 (Box 1)
    - Thomas Fryer Portfolio M.Arch I 2nd Year 2011, 2012-A-099.0054; 1 (Box 1)
  - Gage, Stephen Gary, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
    - Stephen Gage Portfolio Submission, 2012-A-099.0055; 1 (Box 1)
    - Gage - Stephen Portfolio, 2012-A-099.0056; 1 (Box 1)
  - Galetto, Francesco Thiele Dario, 2012; 2012-A-099.0057; 1 (Box 1)
  - Gase, Anthony William, 2012; 2012-A-099.0058; 1 (Box 1)
  - Gettys, Mark, 2011; 2012-A-099.0059; 1 (Box 1)
  - Gridley, William Grandison, 2011; 2012-A-099.0060; 1 (Box 1)
  - Gundersen, Gregory William, 2011; 2012-A-099.0061; 1 (Box 1)
  - Haber, Elizabeth Rose, 2011; 2012-A-099.0062; 1 (Box 1)
  - Hahn Janice Yumi, 2011; 2012-A-099.0063; 1 (Box 1)
  - Hayles, Clay Callaway, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
    - 2011 Spring M.Arch I Design Review Hayles, Clay, 2012-A-099.0064; 1 (Box 1)
    - Clay Hayles Portfolio Spring 2012, 2012-A-099.0065; 1 (Box 1)
  - Heaps, Zachary John, 2012; 2012-A-099.0066; 1 (Box 1)
  - Hedde, Justin Charles, 2011; 2012-A-099.0067; 1 (Box 1)
  - Heineman, Zachary Russell, 2011; 2012-A-099.0068; 1 (Box 1)
  - Herrmann, Erik William, 2012; 2012-A-099.0069; 1 (Box 1)
  - Hochman, Lindsay Nicole, 2011; 2012-A-099.0070; 1 (Box 1)
  - Holborn, Michael Theodore, 2012; 2012-A-099.0071; 1 (Box 1)
  - Hooks, Marcus Addison, 2012; 2012-A-099.0072; 1 (Box 1)
  - Hsu, Rachel Ching-Mei, 2011; 2012-A-099.0073; 1 (Box 1)
  - Hsu, Shirley Nan-Shing, 2011; 2012-A-099.0074; 1 (Box 1)
  - Hsu, Vivian Shing-Wei, 2011; 2012-A-099.0075; 1 (Box 1)
  - Hu, Margaret, 2012; 2012-A-099.0076; 1 (Box 1)
  - Huh, Kyu Young, 2011; 2012-A-099.0077; 1 (Box 1)
  - Johns, Keith Martin, 2011; 2012-A-099.0078; 1 (Box 1)
  - Jourden, John Joseph II, 2011; 2012-A-099.0079; 1 (Box 1)
  - Jung, Homin, 2011; 2012-A-099.0080; 1 (Box 1)
  - Kairam, Seema Saraswati, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
    - Seema Kairam Design Review Final Portfolio, 2012-A-099.0081; 1 (Box 1)
    - Seema Kairam Yale School of Architecture Class of 2012, 2012-A-099.0082; 1 (Box 1)
  - Kane, Douglas Joseph, 2011; 2012-A-099.0083; 1 (Box 1)
  - Kalomiris, Daphne Michelle, 2012; 2012-A-099.0084; 1 (Box 1)
  - Kemper, Anne Mason, 2011; 2012-A-099.0085; 1 (Box 1)
  - Kim, Bryan Hyung Rok, 2012; 2012-A-099.0086; 1 (Box 1)
  - Kim, Jin Hyu, 2011; 2012-A-099.0087; 1 (Box 1)
  - Kiss, Alexandra, 2011; 2012-A-099.0088; 1 (Box 1)
  - Koetter, Alfred Kim, 2011; 2012-A-099.0089; 1 (Box 1)
  - Ku, Gary Tein-Li, 2011; 2012-A-099.0090; 1 (Box 1)
  - Kunstadt, Scott, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
    - 2011 Spring M.Arch 1 Design Review Kunstadt, Scott, 2012-A-099.0091; 1 (Box 1)
    - Scott Kunstadt M.Arch I 2012, 2012-A-099.0092; 1 (Box 1)
  - Lenehan, Kathryn Larkin, 2012; 2012-A-099.0093; 1 (Box 1)
  - Lew, Kee Hyun, 2011; 2012-A-099.0094; 1 (Box 1)
  - Liang, Qi Wei, 2011; 2012-A-099.0095; 1 (Box 1)
  - Lim, Ronald Chyi-Tung, 2011; 2012-A-099.0096; 1 (Box 1)
  - Lombardi, Lisa Marie, 2011; 2012-A-099.0097; 1 (Box 1)
  - Lowry, Liam Patrick, 2010-2011 (Box 1)
    - Spring 2011 M.Arch I Liam Lowry, 2012-A-099.0098; 1 (Box 1)
    - Liam Lowry M.Arch I, 2012-A-099.0099; 1 (Box 1)
  - Markiewicz, Daniel Gregory, 2011; 2012-A-099.0100; 1 (Box 1)
  - Melikyan, Artem Arikovich, 2009-2011 (Box 1)
    - Artem Melikyan Portfolio (Fall 2009-Spring 2010) M.Arch II First Year, 2012-A-099.0101; 1 (Box 1)
    - Artem Melikyan Porfolio M.Arch II (Graduating), 2012-A-099.0102; 1 (Box 1)
  - Mikhaeil, Amir, 2011-2012 (Box 1)
    - 2011 Spring M.Arch I Design Review Amir Mikhaeil, 2012-A-099.0103; 1 (Box 1)
    - Amir Mikhaeil M.Arch I 2012 Porfolio, 2012-A-099.0104; 1 (Box 1)
  - Modesitt, Greta Kristin, 2012; 2012-A-099.0105; 1 (Box 1)
  - Nakarado, Christian Hart, 2011-2012 (Box 2)
  - Nanavatty, Veer Rostum, 2012; 2012-A-099.0108; 1 (Box 2)
  - Narimatsu, Yoshie, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Nee, Diana, 2011-2012 (Box 2)
    - 2011 Design Review M.Arch I Diana Nee Portfolio, 2012-A-099-0111; 1 (Box 2)
    - Diana Nee Design Review Final Portfolio 2012, 2012-A-099-0112; 1 (Box 2)
  - O'Daly, Emer Therese, 2011; 2012-A-099-0113; 1 (Box 2)
  - Ottinger, Emily Sullivan, 2011; 2012-A-099-0114; 1 (Box 2)
  - Ozburn, Ashley Lauren, 2012; 2012-A-099-0115; 1 (Box 2)
  - Ponto, Maureen Nicks, 2011-2012 (Box 2)
    - Maureen Ponto's Portfolio, 2012-A-099-0116; 1 (Box 2)
    - Maureen Ponto Portfolio 2012, 2012-A-099-0117; 1 (Box 2)
  - Putnam, Nancy Li, 2012; 2012-A-099-0118; 1 (Box 2)
  - Rick, Anne Lane, 2011-2012 (Box 2)
    - Lane Rick Spring 2011 Portfolio, 2012-A-099-0119; 1 (Box 2)
    - Ann Lane Rick 2012 Spring M.Arch I Design Final Review, 2012-A-099-0120; 1 (Box 2)
  - Rouben, Dawood Farid, 2012; 2012-A-099-0121; 1 (Box 2)
  - Rowen, Jonah Asher, 2011; 2012-A-099-0122; 1 (Box 2)
  - Saint Claire, Nathan Glennen, 2012; 2012-A-099-0123; 1 (Box 2)
  - Schrader, James Duggan, 2011; 2012-A-099-0124; 1 (Box 2)
  - Schmeck, Karl A., 2011-2012 (Box 2)
    - Karl Schmeck May 9, 2011, 2012-A-099-0125; 1 (Box 2)
    - Karl Schmeck Yale Grad Portfolio May 2012, 2012-A-099-0126; 1 (Box 2)
  - Shigemi, Katsunori, 2011; 2012-A-099-0127; 1 (Box 2)
  - Shin, Seo Young, 2011; 2012-A-099-0128; 1 (Box 2)
  - Smith-Rasmussen, Andrew Benjamin, 2011; 2012-A-099-0129; 1 (Box 2)
  - Sobczak, James Edward, 2011-2012 (Box 2)
    - James Sobczak M.Arch I Design Review, 2012-A-099-0130; 1 (Box 2)
    - 2012 Spring M.Arch I Final review Sobczak, James, 2012-A-099-0131; 1 (Box 2)
  - Spring, Brian Douglas, 2012-A-099-0132; 1 (Box 2)
  - Starling, Ian Gordon, 2012; 2012-A-099-0133; 1 (Box 2)
  - Steiner, Jeremy David, 2011-2012 (Box 2)
    - Jeremy Steiner Spring 2011, 2012-A-099-0134; 1 (Box 2)
    - 2012 Spring M.Arch I Final Portfolio Review Jeremy Steiner, 2012-A-099-0135; 1 (Box 2)
  - Stover, Kyle Richard, 2011; 2012-A-099-0136; 1 (Box 2)
  - Surface, Susan Hideko, 2007-2011; 2012-A-099-0137; 1 (Box 2)
  - Survant, Tyler G., 2011; 2012-A-099-0138; 1 (Box 2)
  - Tailer, Alexandra Fox, 2011; 2012-A-099-0139; 1 (Box 2)
  - Talbot, Mark, 2011; 2012-A-099-0140; 1 (Box 2)
  - Tasman, David Andrwe, 2012; 2012-A-099-0141; 1 (Box 2)
  - Thai Dahn T., 2011; 2012-A-099-0142; 1 (Box 2)
  - Trigg, Justin Terrance, 2012; 2012-A-099-0143; 1 (Box 2)
  - Wagner, Laura Clark, 2011-2012 (Box 2)
    - 2011 Spring M.Arch I Design Review Wagner, Laura, 2012-A-099-0144; 1 (Box 2)
    - 2012 Spring M.Arch I Design Final Review Wagner, Laura, 2012-A-099-0145; 1 (Box 2)
  - Waltersdorfer, Francisco Jesus, 2011; 2012-A-099-0146; 1 (Box 2)
  - Welch, Ryan, 2011; 2012-A-099-0147; 1 (Box 2)
  - Woehrle, Craig A., 2012; 2012-A-099-0148; 1 (Box 2)
  - Yang, David Kihyok, 2011; 2012-A-099-0149; 1 (Box 2)
  - Yang, Guang, 2011; 2012-A-099-0150; 1 (Box 2)
  - Yeo, Jia-Jun, 2011; 2012-A-099-0151; 1 (Box 2)
  - Yoon, Ji-Young, 2011; 2012-A-099-0152; 1 (Box 2)
  - Zahn, Eric Douglas, 2012; 2012-A-099-0153; 1 (Box 2)
  - Zeifman, Emmett, 2011; 2012-A-099-0154; 1 (Box 2)
  - Zhai, Shuo, 2011-2012 (Box 2)
    - Shuo Zhai M.Arch I Review May 2011, 2012-A-099-0155; 1 (Box 2)
    - Shuo Zhai YSOA Porfolio 2012 Spring M.Arch I Design Final Review, 2012-A-099-0156; 1 (Box 2)
  - Zych, Matthew Aaron, 2011; 2012-A-099-0157; 1 (Box 2)
- Master of Environmental Design (M.E.D.) theses, 2004-2012; Accession 2014-A-057
  - Casey, Valerie, The Museum's Object: An Analysis of Contemporary Museology, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - John-Alder, Kathleen L., Ecology Unbound: Revealing the Urban Imagination of Ian McHarg, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Falconer, Iben Andrea, Danish by Design: Architecture, Nationalism, and Promotion, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Pantelidou, Olga, Transaction Space: Architecture, Banking, Technology, and Law, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sadighian, David Bijan, Informing Publics: Museums, Mass Media, Informatics (1964-1977), 2010 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Tombus, Ozlem Caglar, National Identity, Power and Architectural Culture: Three Cases in Istanbul, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - White, Zachary M., Fairy Tale and Myth in (Post-) Modern Chicago Architecture: Thomas Beeby's (Self-) Critical Histories, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Puurunen, Eero, Assessing Environmental Sustainability of Urban Plans: Case Study Helsinki, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Rinehart, David R., Ambientismo and the Modern Style in the Architecture of Marcello Piacentini, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Stamp, Jimmy, Architecture in Medias Rez, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Gin, Matthew Thomas, "Ein Platz und Eine Idee": Designing, Building, and Diffusing the 1972 Munich Olympics, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Marquit, Amanda, At Home in America: An Examination of Motels and Trailers as Low-Income Housing on Commercial Thoroughfares, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sheerin, David, Covert Space: National Security Infrastructure in the Northern Virginia Technology Corridor, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Class of 2014 portfolios [computer files], Accession 2014-A-079 (Box 1)
  - M.Arch I portfolios
    - Artemel, Ali John Pierre (A.J.), 2014
    - Bhalla, Jasdeep, 2014
    - Burr, Mary, 2014
    - Burt, David, 2014
    - Cannavino, Robert (Bobby), 2014
    - Chan, Chun (Henry), 2014
    - Collins, Tyler (Seth), 2014
    - Connolly, Ryan, 2014
    - Davis, Danielle, 2014
    - de la Selle, Violette, 2014
    - Dobson, Evan, 2014
    - Farr, Ivan, 2014
    - Gertler, Clark (Chessin), 2014
    - Hall, Brandon, 2014
    - Han, Jing, 2014
    - Hickox, Charles, 2014
    - Hong, Brian, 2014
    - Jacobs, Daniel, 2014
    - Johnson, Ann, 2014
    - Kow, Jacqueline, 2014
    - Lee, Kyeong Jae (K.J.), 2014
    - LeStourgeon, Russell, 2014
    - Maddock, Bryan, 2014
    - McAdoo, Nicholas (Nick), 2014
    - McPhail, Leeland, 2014
    - Medek, Thomas, 2014
    - Mueller, Christian, 2014
    - Nazmy, Mohamed, 2014
    - Nguyen, Justin, 2014
    - Oncescu, Cristian, 2014
    - Parks, Scott, 2014
    - Pinto-Handler, Talia, 2014
    - Plasencia, Allen (not submitted)
    - Roberts, Jason, 2014
    - Sassaroli, Alexander (Alex), 2014
    - Sheridan, William (Will), 2014
    - Stranix, Kathleen (Kate), 2014
    - Sun, Kailun, 2014
    - Sun, Xiaodi, 2014
    - Svilokos, Ian (not submitted)
    - Swendris, Jonathan (Jon), 2014
    - Tai, Alice, 2014
    - Taubinsky, Nika, 2014
    - Tuminski, Mark, 2014
    - Utting, Brittany, 2014
    - Vale, Constance, 2014
    - VanAcker, Caroline, 2014
    - Warren, Kate, 2014
    - Wiskup, Evan, 2014
  - M.Arch II portfolios
    - Farrace, John, 2014
    - Ghosh, Swarnabh, 2014
    - Greenfield, Daniel, 2014
    - Han, Yoojin, 2014
    - Hintz, Alicia, 2014
    - Kim, Hochung, 2014
    - Lee, Stephanie, 2014
    - Maheshwari, Mansi, 2014
    - McGrattan, Michael, 2014
    - Measham, Eleanor (Bass Scholar), 2014
    - Nawratil, Miron, 2014
    - Petty, James, 2014
    - Rauch, Matthew (Matt), 2014
    - Rossman, Craig, 2014
    - Scott, Jonathan (Grant), 2014
    - Tian, Jie, 2014
    - Tsai, Jay, 2014
    - Yu, Mengyao, 2014
- Class of 2015 portfolios [computer files], Accession 2016-A-030
  - M.Arch I portfolios
    - Abrams, Leah, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Maya, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Amora, Alexander, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Baranes, Elena, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Bell, Emily, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Bhatty, Hiba, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Biczykowski, Kara Marie, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Bridges, Amanda N., 2015 (Box 1)
    - Chastain, Alissa Yen, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Cho, Dionysus, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Cho, Stanley, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Chung, Suhni, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Cohen, Michael R, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Friddle, Thomas, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Gebremichael, Tamrat, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Hancock, Bruce David, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Huelsing, Zachary, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Jang, Tyson, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Jung, Haelee, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Kim, Julie, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Le, Peter Khuong, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Lee, Belinda, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Lee, Hyeun Jason, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Lee, Minu, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Lee, Mun Hee, 2015 (Box 1)
    - McAllister, Meghan, 2015 (Box 1)
    - McClellan, William Ross, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Mezza, Henry Thomas, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Miller, Michael Christopher, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Muraglia, Nicholas, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Nakamura, Phillip, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Ng, Hui Zhen, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Nguyen, Daniel, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Okai, Junpei, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Pertman, Tyler, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Peterson, Mark, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Raab, Lauren, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Sabbagh, Mahdi, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Scott, Robert, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Smith, Benjamin Lucas, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Smith, Sarah, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Su, Amy, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Sun, Jonathan Feng, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Veach, Zachary Adam, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Vega, Emau, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Wexelberg, Perry S., 2015 (Box 1)
    - White, Matthew Hastings, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Wolfe, Jack Blakely, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Yen, Rushyan, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Zhang, Sheena, 2015 (Box 1)
  - M.Arch II portfolios
    - Czeczek, Karolina, 2015 (Box 1)
    - De La Fontaine, Raphael, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Futo, Julia, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Hoxha, Elvira, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Jazmines, Stephanie Anne Arrienda, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Karminpour, Amir Andrew, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Li, Mengran, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Li, Yifan, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Lisi, Kate Alexandra, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Lumley, Laurence Peter Esmond, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Luster, Daniel James, 2015 (Box 1)
    - McInish, Peter Allen, Jr., 2015 (Box 1)
    - Milholland, Olen Snow, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Spencer, Ian Stewart, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Wagoner, Adam Ramsey, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Yu Kin Tak, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Zhang, Boyuan, 2015 (Box 1)
- Master of Environmental Design (M.E.D.) theses, 2009, 2013-2014; Accession 2016-A-064
  - Kalpacki, Andreas, Unleashing Citizenship: Internationalism and the Project of the World (1899-1914), 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Blane, Saga, XS: A Play in Four Parts, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Salcedo, Juana, Taming El Dorado: Planning Misadventures in the Venezuela Guyana, 1951-1964, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Daga, Anuj, In the Place of Images, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Qureshi, Ayeza Rahat, Mapping Power: the Political Instrumentality of the Map in Karachi, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Snyder, Daniel E. III, The Tender Detail: Ornament and Sentimentality from Louis H. Sullivan to Frank Lloyd Wright, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Varner, Jessica, Biology, Expertise and Exchange CoEvolution Quarterly, 1974-1984, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Student year end work, M. Arch I [born digital files] (Box 1)
  - Doreen Adengo M Arch. I, 2006-A-043-0001; 1 (Box 1)
  - Benjamin Albertson Disk 1 of 2, 2006-A-043-0002; 1 (Box 1)
  - Benjamin Albertson Disk 2 of 2, 2006-A-043-0003; 1 (Box 1)
  - Francesca Russello Amon M.E.D. Thesis May 2005, 2006-A-043-0004; 1 (Box 1)
  - Daniel Barber "People's Park" MED Thesis '05, 2006-A-043-0005; 1 (Box 1)
  - [no lable information], 2006-A-043-0006; 1 (Box 1)
  - YSOA Nora I. Bergsten M Arch I 2005 Portfolio PDF, 2006-A-043-0007; 1 (Box 1)
  - Ceren Bingol YSOA Work - May 2005, 2006-A-043-0008; 1 (Box 1)
  - March II Brent Buck Portfolio and Exhibit PDFs '05, 2006-A-043-0009; 1 (Box 1)
  - Eimone Brotl MED 2005, 2006-A-043-0010; 1 (Box 1)
  - Yen-Rong Chen MArch I 2005 Disk 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0011; 1 (Box 1)
  - Kevin Conway MArch I 2005 Final Portfolio Final Exhibit Board 5-13-05 PDF format, 2006-A-043-0012; 1 (Box 1)
  - Michael Cook MArch I 2005 Portfolio images (and exhibition) jpeg/tiff 1/1, 2006-A-043-0013; 1 (Box 1)
  - Lois Donovan M. Arch II 2005 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0014; 1 (Box 1)
  - William M. Dudley M.Arch I 2005 Disk #1 of 8, 2006-A-043-0015; 1 (Box 1)
  - William M. Dudley M.Arch I 2005 Disk #2 of 8, 2006-A-043-0016; 1 (Box 1)
  - William M. Dudley M.Arch I 2005 Disk #3 of 8, 2006-A-043-0017; 1 (Box 1)
  - William M. Dudley M.Arch I 2005 Disk #4 of 8, 2006-A-043-0018; 1 (Box 1)
  - William M. Dudley M.Arch I 2005 Disk #5 of 8, 2006-A-043-0019; 1 (Box 1)
  - William M. Dudley M.Arch I 2005 Disk #6 of 8, 2006-A-043-0020; 1 (Box 1)
  - William M. Dudley M.Arch i 2005 Disk #7 of 8, 2006-A-043-0021; 1 (Box 1)
  - William M. Dudley M.Arch I 2005 Disk 8 of 8, 2006-A-043-0022; 1 (Box 1)
  - William M. Dudley M.Arch I 2005 Poster, 2006-A-043-0023; 1 (Box 1)
  - Christopher Fein MArch II 2005 Portfolio Disk 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0024; 1 (Box 1)
  - Rosamond Fletcher MED '05, 2006-A-043-0025; 1 (Box 1)
  - Mathew Ford M.Arch I 2005, 2006-A-043-0026; 1 (Box 1)
  - Ashley McRainey Forde M.ARch I 2005 Disk 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0027; 1 (Box 1)
  - g.fu MARch I 2005 disk 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0028; 1 (Box 1)
  - James Fulton III; M.Arch. I 2005; Disk 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0029; 1 (Box 1)
  - Portfolio Jonah Gamblin MArch I 2005, 2006-A-043-0030; 1 (Box 1)
  - Garth Goldstein MArch I 2005 Portfolio, 2006-A-043-0031; 1 (Box 1)
  - Final Portfolio 1 of 1 MArch I 2005 Charles Gosrisirikur, 2006-A-043-0032; 1 (Box 1)
  - Ruth Gyuse Final PDF Portfolio May 2005, 2006-A-043-0033; 1 (Box 1)
  - Christopher Hall MArch II 2005, 2006-A-043-0034; 1 (Box 1)
  - Portfolio Mark Hash MArch II 2005, 2006-A-043-0035; 1 (Box 1)
  - David Hecht MArch I 2005 Portfolio.pdf, Exhibition.pdf, Feldman.pdf Yale School of Architecture Digital Archive, 2006-A-043-0036; 1 (Box 1)
  - Derek Hoeferlin MArch II, 2005 Disc 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0037; 1 (Box 1)
  - LiHan Hong MED Thesis Observing Shadows, 2006-A-043-0038; 1 (Box 1)
  - Portfolio, Feldman BDS.05, End of Year BD.05 Portfolio_Matt_Hutchinson_05, 2006-A-043-0039; 1 (Box 1)
  - Jean Y. Kim M.Arch I 2005 Archive CD: Contains Exhibit Poster pdf and Portfolio pdf, 2006-A-043-0040; 1 (Box 1)
  - Jesse J. Lafreneire Yale 2005 M.Arch 1 Yale School of Architecture Gallery: SHIFT, 2006-A-043-0041; 1 (Box 1)
  - Louis Lee M.Arch I 2005 Portfolio, 2006-A-043-0042; 1 (Box 1)
  - Sang Yup Lee Portfolio and Exhibition, 2006-A-043-0043; 1 (Box 1)
  - Lee Lim Master of Architecture, 2005 Poster File and Portfolio PDF, 2006-A-043-0044; 1 (Box 1)
  - amanda.loy@yale.edu Portfolio pdf 05/2005 M.Arch I, 2006-A-043-0045; 1 (Box 1)
  - Craig Grant Morton M.Arch I YSOA 2005, 2006-A-043-0046; 1 (Box 1)
  - Jennifer Newsom Yale University Archives Portfolio 05-16-05, 2006-A-043-0047; 1 (Box 1)
  - Guvenc Ozel 2005, 2006-A-043-0048; 1 (Box 1)
  - Brandon Pace March 11 2005 Contents: Portfolio Grad Board Feldman.504 Feldman.F04, 2006-A-043-0049; 1 (Box 1)
  - Michael Lee Poy Own Earth 4 Black Narratives, 2006-A-043-0050; 1 (Box 1)
  - Michael Rey YSUA Portfolio March 1 2005, 2006-A-043-0051; 1 (Box 1)
  - George Ristow M.Arch.I 2005 Disk 1 of 1 portfolio pdf, 2006-A-043-0052; 1 (Box 1)
  - Vanessa Ruff Portfolio M.Arch I 2005, 2006-A-043-0053; 1 (Box 1)
  - Aniket Shahane M.Arch 2 205 Disc 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0054; 1 (Box 1)
  - Yale School of Architecture Shift Year End Exhibit of Student Work 2004-2005 Noah Shepherd M.Arch I Exhibit Poster Feldman Poster Portfolio Read Me File .pdf files., 2006-A-043-0055; 1 (Box 1)
  - Brett Spearman March 11 2005 Disk 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0056; 1 (Box 1)
  - Nicholas Stoutt M.Arch I 2005 Disk 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0057; 1 (Box 1)
  - Yony Teperman M.Arch I 2005 Portfolio PDF, 2006-A-043-0058; 1 (Box 1)
  - Brad Walters MED Thesis 2004, 2006-A-043-0059; 1 (Box 1)
  - Author: Lewis Wadsworth Program: M.Arch I Graduation: 2005, 2006-A-043-0060; 1 (Box 1)
  - Sal Wilson - M.Arch I 2005 Portfolio [- 2 volumes] Mario Gooden Studio [missing links from portfolio], 2006-A-043-0061; 1 (Box 1)
  - Christopher Yost M.Arch II Program 2005 disk 1 of 1, 2006-A-043-0062; 1 (Box 1)
  - Yale's Archive Yu, Waiki Tracy Posr-Pro Class of 2005 disk 01 of 01, 2006-A-043-0063; 1 (Box 1)
- Master of Environmental Design theses, 2016-2018; Accession 2019-A-0037
  - Morris, Geneva "Life in One Room: Small Space Living Typologies, 1940-2015", 2016 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Talwai, Preeti "Self, Space, Screen: Embodied Relationships in Hybrid Retail Environments", 2016 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cartelli, Gregory "Strategic Model Theater: The Urban Training Facility and the (re)Production of the City, 1943-2016", 2017 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Weng, Jia (Jane) "Waste in the Water Machine: Pathologies of the Three Rivers Gorge Project", 2018 (Box 1, Folder 4)